anytimeproperty.com 2009-04-22

# Real Estate Property India | Leading Real Estate Portal | Properties for Sale in Chennai India | Buy Sell Rent Residential Property India | Commercial Property in India | Real Estate Listings.

Anytimeproperty.com website is owned and operated by Anytime Infotech Pvt Ltd (Formerly known as Anytimeproperty.Com Pvt Ltd). We have created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to our user's privacy.

**What information you need to give in to use this site?**

Anytimeproperty.com gathers information from users who apply for the various services of our site. It includes email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number or other contact number and fax number if exists. We also collect additional information about user's property.

**How the site uses the information it collects/tracks?**

Anytimeproperty.com collects information from our clients primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver personalized experience.

**With whom the site shares the information it collects/tracks?**

The information collected from any of our clients is shared with their approval to individuals and organizations.  
Except where you are explicitly informed, Anytimeproperty.com do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information. 

**Partnering With Others**

Anytimeproperty.com may tie-up with partners to bring you various services. However, we will never share your personal information, without your explicitly permission. Still, we encourage you to review the privacy policy of the partner for questions about their use, any personally identifiable information that you may separately submit to such partner.

Anytimeproperty.com contains links to other websites. Anytime Infotech Pvt Ltd (Formerly known as Anytimeproperty.Com Pvt Ltd) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Troubleshooting the problems**

We may use IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address may be also used to gather broad demographic information. 

**Links to third party companies**

We may use a third party ad company to display ads on [anytimeproperty.com](http://anytimeproperty.com/index.php). These ads may contain cookies. While we may use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.  

**Notice**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments or as a result of a change of policy in our company. We will prominently post a link to those changes on our Homepage so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If you have any questions regarding this statement, please write to us: [Contact Us](http://anytimeproperty.com/index.php?pg=contactus)
